Finding Aid for the Tennessee Screenwriting Association Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Ralph J. Bunche Papers
1988-2002
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0442
.84 linear_feet
Scope and Content Note
This collection is made up of materials in 2 Hollinger boxes comprising .84 linear feet.
It includes correspondence, newsletters, newspaper articles, photographs,by - laws and other documents relating to the Association covering the years 1988 to 2002.
- Correspondence
  - Incoming, outgoing - Anne Taylor (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marice Wolfe (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Documents
  - By-Laws of Tennessee Screenwriting Associations, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Statement of purpose for TSA, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Papers relating to the TSA - Internal Revenue Service, State of Tennessee and other (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Newsletters
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 3, no.1; Vol. 3, no.2; Vol.3, no.4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 4, no.1 - 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 5, no. 1 - 4, Spring 1992 - Winter 1992/ 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol.6, no. 1 - 4; Vol. 7, no. no. 1, 2, 4, Spring 1993 - Winter 1994/1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 8, no. 1 - 3; Vol. 9, no. 1, Vol. 10, no. 3 - 4 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 11, no. 6, 7, 9, June, July, October 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 12, no. 2 - 12, February 1999 - December 1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 13, no. 1 - 12, June 2000 - December 2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fade In - Tennessee Screenwriting Association - Vol. 14, no. 05, May 2001; Vol. 15, no. 02, February 2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Tennessee Screenwriting Association, Inc. - Vol. 1, no. 1, Sept. 1998; Vol. 1, no. 2, Winter 1988; Vol. 2, no. 2, Spring 1989; Vol. 2, no. 3, Fall 1989; Vol. 2, no. 4, Winter 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee State of the Arts, Film, Entertainmen, and Music Commission - Vol. 2, no. 2, Summer 1989; Vol. 2, no. 3, Fall 1989; Vol. 3; Vol. 3, no.1, Spring 1990; Vol. 3, no. 3, Fall 1990; Vol. 4, no. 1, Winter 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Wisconsin’s Screenwriters Forum - Vol. VIII, no. 1 - 6, January 1990 - December 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Articles
  - “Williamson Park is “Preserved” on Film” in Mid – Memphian, June/July 1989; City Map of Memphis; Brochure Tennessee State of the Art; other (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Profile of Anne Taylor and TSA in Nashville Business Journal, October 1989 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - “ The Third Woman of ‘Thelma and Louise’ in the New York Times, Wed., June 5, 1991; “Screenwriter: Film not anti – male “ in Vanderbilt Hustler, Vol. 103, no. 49, Tuesday, November 19, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Reviews of Murphy’s Fault by Steven Womack in Publisher’s Weekly, Dec. 8, 1989 and in the New York Times, March 4, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Other materials
  - Screenwriting workshops, programs, announcements, etc. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Screenwriting workshops, programs, announcements, etc. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Screening Schedules - Sarratt Cinema - Vanderbilt University - Summer 1990, Summer 1991, Fall 1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Writers Guild of America - Guidelines and Miscellaneous Papers (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Publication - Memphis Film, Tape, and Music Directory 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Application form - Metropolitan Nashville Arts Commission Grants Programs, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Financial information - Catalog of Services, 1991, Management Development Center, HCA United Way of Middle Tennessee (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Notebook - Records
  - Budgets - 1989 and 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memphis (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Metro Arts Commission, 1990 and 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Newsletters (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Delbert Mann - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Delbert Mann - Newspaper articles (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Delbert Mann - Preview Film Festival and Exhibition of Director’s Papers, April 23 - 25, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Delbert Mann – Photograph - D.M.as guest of TSA, Spring 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Janet Neipris (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tom Rickman (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Tom Rickman - Screenwriting workshop with photographs and related materials (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Tom Schulman, correspondence (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Tom Schulman (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tommy Wallace (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Contacts (1) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Contacts (2) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Contacts (3) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Contacts (4) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Agendas, minutes - Feb. 1989 - June 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Agendas, minutes - July 1990 - January 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Members (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Job Descriptions (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Notebook – Records of Tennessee Film, Tape, and Music Commission
  - Introduction; Table of Contents (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Index; Table of Category abbreviations, pp. 1 - 2; Participants names, categories, phone numbers, pp. 3 - 22 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - (1) Production - Categories in alphabetical order, pp. 23 - 104 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - (2) Production - Categories in alphabetical order, pp. 105 - 160 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - (3) Production - Categories in alphabetical order, pp. 161 - 223 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Post Production - Categories in alphabetical order, pp. 231 - 263 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Major cities information, pp. 265 - 346 Chattanooga, pp. 267 - 282 Jackson, pp. 285 - 292 Knoxville, pp. 293 - 304 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Major cities information, pp. 265 - 346 Memphis, pp. 305 - 318 Nashville, pp. 319 - 334 Tri-cities, pp. 335 - 346 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous: Climate/Weather Information, pp. 349 - 364; Maps, p. 365; Truck and Weight Laws, p. 367; Right- to-Work and Union Information, 367 - - 368; Music Recording/Publishing Services Information, pp. 369; Filmography, pp. 371 - 375 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Materials – Envelopes and Letterhead Stationery for TSA (Box 2, Folder 32)